yageo.com 2013-05-13

# YAGEO

| 

You are Here:Privacy Policy

|  **Policy Overview**  
---  
The Privacy Policy discloses the information that is collected through our website [www.yageo.com](http://www.yageo.com/) and how such information is used. Yageo follows all applicable laws on data privacy protection and data security. The ultimate goal for gathering information is to improve service and support to customers. If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us at[marcom@yageo.com](mailto:marcom@yageo.com). This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information which is collected through this website.  
   
Information Collected  
You do not have to provide any personal information to use this website. But there are certain services on this website which you may wish to subscribe for (such as news subscriptions) that may require you to provide personally identifiable information, such as your name, mailing address, email address and other contact information. If you decide at any time to discontinue receiving mailings from us, please see the paragraph below headed "Modifying or Deleting Personal Information". Our web server automatically records certain information incidental to your use of our website, such as the name of your IP address of the computer you are using, the type of browser software and operating system that you use, and other similar information. Information regarding your and other visitors' traffic patterns may be aggregated to compile a web transaction report to show various web traffic-related information   
   
|  Use of Information Collected  
---  
The personal information collected is used to respond to your inquiries and to send you newsletters that you request. The information collected is also used to help us to maintain and/or upgrade the quality of our website and the services that we provide on the website. We will not disclose, sell or provide such information to unaffiliated third parties; however, we may provide such information to our subsidiaries. We reserve the right to provide such information to our officers, employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to execute certain web services (such as web hosting or maintenance services) for us. We also reserve the right to disclose such information to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any or all of the following: (i) by law; (ii) to comply with legal processes or governmental requests; (iii) to prevent, investigate, detect or prosecute criminal offences or attacks on the technical integrity of the web site or our network; and/or (iv) to protect the rights, property, or safety of Yageo, the users of the website, or the public.   
   
Use of Cookies  
When you view our website, we may store some data on your computer in the form of a "cookie" to automatically recognize your PC next time you visit. Cookies can help us in many ways, for example, by allowing us to tailor a website to better match your interests or to store your password to save you having to re-enter it each time. If you do not wish to receive cookies, please configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your computer's hard drive, block all cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored.  
   
Modifying or Deleting Your Personal Information  
If you wish to modify your personal information, or if you wish to discontinue receiving materials from us or wish to remove your personal information from Yageo's database, you can contact us at [marcom@yageo.com](mailto:marcom@yageo.com)  
   
Consent to Our Privacy Policy   
Your use of our website constitutes your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy as amended or revised by us, and you should therefore review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you know of its terms.
